

Madhusudan Panda

Motion Graphic / Graphic Designer

SKILLS

Creativity
Typography
Technology
Communication

ABOUT ME

Creative graphic designer with innovative ideas and a unique approach to visuals. More than **1.5** years of experience developing designs for mobile apps, online websites, video, and advertising. Solid understanding of marketing principles and advertising techniques. Great attention to detail and a talent for creating memorable visual designs.

SOFTWARE

Management

Photoshop

Illustrator
Premiere
After effects
Adobe XD

EDUCATION

2010-2012 CHSE,ODISHA
Council of higher secondary education in (Arts)

2012-2015 SCTE & VT,ODISHA
Diploma in (Mechanical Engineering).

2015-2018 BPUT,ODISHA
Bachelor of Technology in (Mechanical Engineering).

LANGUAGES

English
Hindi
Oriya

CONTACT

9861616961

Hyderabad, Telangana

EXPERIENCE

2018-2019

NSDC

National Skill Development

Corporation (Skill India) as a Assessor.

Designer in Tradin project.

2019-present Genii IT Services Pvt. Ltd.

Working as a UX/MotionGraphic/Graphic

HOBBIES



https://grafo-designer.github.io/grafo/

madhusudan.panda1@gmail.com

